Guide to the Lesly Lempert Collection, 1987-1994.
Lempert, Lesly Collection
- Series I. Periodicals
  - (World Conference on Human Rights): Land Ownership and Use, June, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - (World Conference on Human Rights): The Unrecognised Villages, June, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Remember the Forgotten Faithful, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    Producer: Arab Christian Church in the Middle East
  - Annual Report 1989, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    Producer: Association for Civil Rights in Israel
  - The Legal and Administrative System (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Newsletter, Spring 1991--Spring 1992 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    Producer: Association for Israel Studies
    Volume/Number: 6.2, 7.2
  - Activities Report, July 1990--November 1992 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    Producer: Association of Israeli-Palestinian Physicians for Human Rights (AIPPHR)
  - (Activities Report): 1988-1990, July, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): June-July 1990, June/July 1990 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): August-September 1990, August/September 1990 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): January-February 1990, January/February 1991 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): October 1991's Report, October, 1991; photocopy, 3 leaves (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): Report of Activities-January 1992, January, 1992; photocopy, 4 leaves (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): Report of Activities-April 1992, April, 1992; photocopy, 6 leaves (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): The Activities of AIPPHR: Bi-Annual Report, January-July 1992 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): Report of Activites-May June 1992, May/June 1992 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - (Activities Report): Activity Report-July-November 1992: Focus on: Torture in Israel, July-November 1992 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - AIPPHR Representatives Meet with General Freddy Zach, Deputy Coordinator of Activities in the Occupied Territories, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - An open letter to Mr. James Baker, Secretary of State of the United States of America, April 9, 1991; photocopy, 4 leaves (Box 2, Folder 80)
    Producer: Association of Israeli-Palestinian Physicians for Human Rights (AIPPHR), Society of St. Ives
  - Annual Report, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Annual Report focus on: The Transfer of Health Services to a Palestinian Authority, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Basic Principles and Aims of the Association of Israeli and Palestinian Physicians for Human Rights, [?] (Box 2, Folder 82)
    Producer: Association of Israeli- Palestinian Physicians for Human Rights (AIPPHR)
  - Curfew in the Town of Anabata (typescript, 9 pages), [1991?] (Box 2, Folder 84)
    Producer: Association of Israeli-Palestinian Physicians for Human Rights (AIPPHR), Dorit Abramovitch
  - [Newspaper articles covering the AIPPHR conference "The International Struggle against Torture and the Case of Isreal"], [1993]; photocopies, 36 leaves (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Petition for Legislation Against Torture in Israel, [January 1993?]; photocopy, 3 leaves (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Press Release, July, 16, 1990--September 9, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Project Proposal: Conference: The International Struggle Against Torture and The Case of Israel, September, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Report on Rehabilitation Services in the Occupied Territories, August, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    Producer: Association of Israeli-Palestinian Physicians for Human Rights (AIPPHR), Yosef Grodzinsky, Ph.D, Ruhama Marton, M.D.
  - Report on the Condition of Health Services in the Gaza Strip, August, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Yusef Ahmad Ibrahim Hamlawi, May 31, 1990; typescript, 1 page (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Israeli and Palestinian Physicians Respond to Medical Situation in the West Bank and Gaza, August, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    Producer: Association of Israeli and Palestinian Physicians
  - Report on Visit to El-Mukasaad Hospital, Jerusalem Following the Massacrew on the Temple Mount, October 11, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 92 A)
  - The Breakdown of Normal Life and the Health Care System in the Occupied Territories in the Wake of the Imposition of a General Curfew, January, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 92 B)
  - A Policy of Discrimination: Land Expropriation, Planning and Building in East Jerusalem, January, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Eitan Felner
  - Absolute Prohibition: The Torture and Ill-treatment of Palestinian Detainees, May, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Center for the Defence of the Individual, Yehezkel Lein
  - Activity of the Undercover Units in the Occupied Territories, May, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Na'ama Yashuvi
  - B'Tselem Demands that the Israeli Government Immediately Halt the Killing in the Occupied Territories, [1993?]; transmission, 4 leaves (Box 2, Folder 96)
    Producer: B'Tselem
  - The B'Tselem Human Rights Report, Spring 1994--Fall 1997 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    Volume/Number: 2.1, 5.1
  - Captive Corpses, March, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Case Study, September 1992--January 2004 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Volume/Number: 1--5, 7--8, 15, 17--18
  - (Case Study 1): The Death of Mustafa Barakat in the Interrogation Wing of the Tulkarm Prison, September, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yuval Ginbar, Tami Bash
    Volume/Number: 1
  - (Case Study 2): Khan Yunis: December 1992, January, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yuval Ginbar
    Volume/Number: 2
  - (Case Study 3): The "New Procedure" in GSS Interrogation: The Case of 'Abd a-Nasser 'Ubeid, November, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Volume/Number: 3
  - (Case Study 4): Lethal Gunfire and Collective Punishment in the Wake of the Massacre at the Tomb of the Patriarchs, March, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Tami Bash, Yuval Ginbar
    Volume/Number: 4
  - (Case Study 5): Summary Execution: Jabalya Refugee Camp, March 28, 1994, April, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Palestinian Lawyers for Human Rights, Yuval Ginbar
    Volume/Number: 5
  - (Case Study 7): Playing with Fire on the Temple Mount: Use of Lethal and Excessive Force by the Israeli Police Force, December, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Eitan Felner, Yuval Ginbar
    Volume/Number: 7
  - (Case Study 8): Lethal Training: Killing of Muhammad Al-Hilu by Undercover Soldiers in Hizmeh Village, March, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Shirly Eran, Yael Stein
    Volume/Number: 8
  - (Case Study 15): Standing Idly By: Non-enforcement of the Law on Settlers, Hebron 26-28 July 2002, August, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yael Stein
    Volume/Number: 15
  - (Case Study 17): Abuse of Palestinians by IDF Soldiers in Hebron, 3 December 2002, December, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Volume/Number: 17
  - (Case Study 18): Abuse of Palestinians at the Sarra Checkpoint, Nablus District 27-31 December 2003, January, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Volume/Number: 18
  - Collaborators in the Occupied Territories: Human Rights Abuses and Violations, January, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yizhar Be'er, Dr. Saleh 'Abdel-Jawad
  - Demolition and Sealing of Houses as a Punitive Measure in the West Bank and the Gaza Strip During the Intifada, September, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Ronny Talmor
  - Deportation of Palestinians from the Occupied Territories and the Mass Deportation of December 1992, June, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    Producer: B'Tselem, (multiple authors)
  - The Gaza Strip-One Big Prison (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Drawings of prisoners (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Information Sheet: Update (English version), August 1, 1989--September/October [1992] (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Intifada Fatalities/Special Report-Prison Facilities, August 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Intifada Fatalities/Administrative Detention, September 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Banned Books and Authors, October 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Daphna Golan
  - (Information Sheet): Intifada Fatalities/Soldiers' Trials/Restrictions on Foreign Travel, November 1, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Na'ama Yashuvi, Yuval Ginbar
  - (Information Sheet): Intifada Fatalities/Cases of Death and Injury of Children, January 1, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Intifada Fatalities/Censorship of the Palestinian Press in East Jerusalem, February/March 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Intifada Fatalities/IDF Posts on Private Homes/Purimshpiel in 'Abud/Followup Investigation: The Death of Rafaida Abu Laban, April, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Intifada Fatalities/The Military Judicial System in the West Bank: Followup Report, May, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - The Military Judicial system in the West Bank, November, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Violence Against Minors in Police Detention, June/July 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Limitations on Building of Residences on the West Bank, August, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Closure of Schools and Other Setbacks to the Education System in the Occupied Territories, October, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Dafna Na'or
  - (Information Sheet): House Demolition and Sealing as a Form of Punishment in the West Bank and Gaza Strip: Followup Report, November, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - (Information Sheet): Human Rights in the Occupied Territories During the War in the Persian Gulf, January/February 1991, January 2009-April 2010, January 1991--April 2010 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Daphna Golan, Yuval Ginbar
  - (Information Sheet): The Death of a Youth: Mahmud 'Alayan/Maltreatment by an Income Tax Clerk/Pressure on Families of Wanted Persons/Intifada Fatalities, June, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Roni Talmor
  - (Information Sheet): Complaints of Human Rights Violations in the Israeli-Occupied Territories, August, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Center for the Defence of the Individual, Sharon Roubach
  - (Information Sheet): Renewal of Deportation of Women and Children from the Occupied Territories on Account of "Illegal Residency", September/October [1992] (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yuval Ginbar, Bassem 'Eid
  - Information Sheet, April 1993--December 1998 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - (Information Sheet): The Closure of the West Bank and Gaza Strip: Human Rights Violations Against Residents of the Occupied Territories, April, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Daphna Golan, Tami Bash
  - (Information Sheet): Limitations on the Right to Demonstrate and Protest in the Territories, January, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - (Information Sheet): House Demolition During Operations Against Wanted Persons, May, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yuval Ginbar, Roni Talmor
  - (Information Sheet): The Killing of Palestinian Children Against the Open-Fire Regulations, June, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - (Information Sheet): Firing at Vehicles by the Secuirty Forces in the Occupied Territories, February, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - (Information Sheet): Without Limits: Human Rights Violations Under Closure, April, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Noga Kadman
  - (Information Sheet): Sexual Harassment in the Name of the Law: Violence and Degradation during Searches of Palestinian Homes in Hebron, December, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - (Information Sheet): Demolishing Peace: Israel's Policy of Mass Demolition of Palestinian Houses in the West Bank, September, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - (Information Sheet): Disputed Waters: Israel's Responsibility for the Water Shortage in the Occupied Territories, September, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yehezkel Lein
  - (Information Sheet): Death Foretold: Firing of "Rubber" Bullets to Disperse Demonstrations in the Occupied Territories, December, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Information Sheet, July 1999--July 2005 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - (Information Sheet): On the Way to Annexation: Human Rights Violations Resulting from the Establishment and Expansion of the Ma'aleh Adumim Settlement, July, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - (Information Sheet): Trigger Happy: Unjustified Shooting and Violation of the Open-Fire Regulations during the al-Aqsa Intifada, March, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Ron Dudai
  - (Information Sheet): Not All it Seems: Preventing Palestinians Access to Their Lands West of the Separation Barrier in the Tulkarm-Qalqiliya Area, June, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Shlomi Swisa
  - (Information Sheet): Take No Prisoners: The Fatal Shooting of Palestinians by Israeli Security Forces during "Arrest Operations", May, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Ronen Shnayderman
  - (Information Sheet): Means of Expulsion: Violence, Harassment and Lawlessness against Palestinians in the Southern Hebron Hills, July, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Antigona Ashkar
  - (Information Sheet): Barred from Contact: Violation of the Right to Visit Palestinians Held in Israeli Prisons, September, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - (Information Sheet): Forbidden Roads: Israel's Discriminatory Road Regime in the West Bank, August, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - The Interrogation of Palestinians During the Intifada, March 1991--March 1992 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - (The Interrogation of Palestinians During the Intifada): Ill-treatment, "Moderate Physical Pressure" or Torture?, March, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Stanley Cohen, Daphna Golan
  - (The Interrogation of Palestinians During the Intifada): Follow-up to March 1991 B'Tselem Report, March, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Land Grab: Israel's Settlement Policy in the West Bank, May, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Law Enforcement vis-à-vis Israeli Civilians in the Occupied Territories, March, 1994; transmission, 19 leaves (Box 3, Folder 109)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Eitan Felner, Roli Rozen
  - Legitimizing Torture: The Israeli High Court of Justice Rulings in the Bilbeisi, Hamdan and Mubarak Cases: An Annotated Sourcebook, January, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Yuval Ginbar, Jessica Montell
  - [Letter to Yitshaq Shamir, Defense Minister and Prime Minister, with attached testimony], May 13, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Zahalah Galon (signed)
  - Loss of Control: The Temple Mount Events-Preliminary Investigation, October 14, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Position Paper, January 2000--March 2003 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - (Position Paper): Legislation Allowing the Use of Physical Force and Mental Coercion in Interrogations by the General Security Service, January, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - (Position Paper): Thirsty for a Solution: The Water Crisis in the Occupied Territories and its Resolution in the Final-Status Agreement, July, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - (Position Paper): Behind the Barrier: Human Rights Violations as a Result of Israel's Separation Barrier, March, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Press Release, February 12, 1990--November 1, 1990; tranmissions, 6 leaves (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - The Quiet Deportation Continues: Revocation of Residency and Denial of Social Rights of East Jerusalem Palestinians, September, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Center for the Defence of the Individual, Yael Stein
  - Status Report, March 2003--September 2006 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - (Status Report): Al-Mawasi, Gaza Strip: Intolerable Life in an Isolated Enclave, March, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - (Status Report): Hebron, Area H-2: Settlements Cause Mass Departure of Palestinians, August, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - (Status Report): Nu'man, East Jerusalem: Life under the Threat of Expulsion, September, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - (Status Report): Facing the Abyss: The Isolation of Sheikh Sa'ad Village-Before and After the Separation Barrier, February, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - (Status Report): Act of Vengeance: Israel's Bombing of the Gaza Power Plant and its Effects, September, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    Producer: B'Tselem, Darryl Li, Yehezkel Lein
  - A Wall in Jerusalem: Obstacles to Human Rights in the Holy City, Summer 2006 (Box 3, Folder 116 A)
  - The Main Points of B'Tselem's Response to the Zamir Commision of Investigation into the Temple Mount Events, [November 12, 1990]; transmittal (Box 3, Folder 116 B)
  - One Big Prison: Freedom of Movement to and from the Gaza Strip on the Eve of the Disengagement Plan, March, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 116 C)
    Producer: Yehezkel Lein, B'Tselem, HaMoked
  - Basic Law: Human Rights (unofficial translation), [?] (Box 3, Folder 116 D)
    Producer: Quaker Legal Aid Service
  - Lawyer's Rendezvous in Gaza, September, 1988; typescript (Box 3, Folder 116 E)
    Producer: Burton Caine
  - The Intifada, The United Nations and the Non-Governmental Organizations, March 29, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 116 F)
    Producer: Don Betz
  - The Use of Firearms by the Security Forces in the Occupied Territories, July, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - The System of Taxation in the West Bank and the Gaza Strip As An Instrument for the Enforcement of Authority During the Uprising, February, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Violations of Human Rights in the Occupied Territories, 1989, 1990/1991--1992/1993 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Crossing the Line: Violation of the Rights of Palestinians in Israel without a Permit, March, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 118 B)
  - Ground to a Halt: Denial of Palestinians' Freedom of Movement in the West Bank, August, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 118 B)
  - Foul Play: Neglect of Wastewater Treatment in the West Bank, June, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 118 C)
  - Access Denied: Israeli Measures to Deny Palestinians Access to Land Around Settlements, September, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 118 C)
  - Without Trial: Administrative Detention of Palestinians by Israel and the Internment of Unlawful Combatants Law, October, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 118 C)
  - Detained without Trial: Administrative Detention in the Occupied Territories Since the Beginning of the Intifada, October, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 118c)
  - By Hook and by Crook: Israeli Settlement Policy in the West Bank, July, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 118 C)
  - Beita, March 24, 1989, March 24, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    Producer: Beita Committee
  - (Hebrew Translation): Beita, March 24, 1989, March 24, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - (Arabic Translation): Beita, March 24, 1989, March 24, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - The Beita Trial Opens, [1988?]; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - The Committee for Beita, [1988?]; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - List of Accused in the Beita Trial and Some Details of Their Indictments, [1989?]; typescript, 1 pages (Box 3, Folder 122)
    Producer: [Beita Committee?]
  - [Packet of information provided by The Bieta Committee about the conflict in Bieta], December 15, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - (Letter of transmittal), December 15, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    Producer: Judy Green
  - (Formal report): Another Beita Incident: The Killing of Shinwar Muhib Abdulrahman Hamayiel, November 30, 1988; typescript, 3 leaves (Box 3, Folder 123)
    Producer: Judith Green
  - Correspondence Regarding the Case pf Sabri Ghuraib from Beit Ijza, April 18 1990 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - (Press release): from the Committee from Beita, November 30, 1988; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - (Report): The Beita Trial, November 21, 1988; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - (Article): Eyewitness: Soldiers vandalized homes; cars in Beita, [1988?]; photocopy, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 123)
    Producer: Joel Greenberg
  - (Article): Despite alibi, judge won't free W. Bank man, [1988?]; photocopy, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 123)
    Producer: Jerusalem Post
  - Press Release, June 27, 1989; typescript, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Making Education Illegal: Students from the Gaza Strip: Israeli restrictions and international reactions, January, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    Producer: Birzeit Univerisity, Nigel Parry
  - Newsletter, July 1992--March 1993 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    Producer: Birzeit Univerisity
    Volume/Number: 22--23
  - CNEWA Reports New "Curfew Petition" Before Israeli High Court, April 4, 1991; photocopy, 1 page (Box 3, Folder 127)
    Producer: Catholic Near East Welfare Association (CNEWA)
  - A Special Report, [June 1992]--October 1994 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine
  - (A Special Report): 25 Years After the 1967 War: U.S. Policy and the Arab-Israeli Conflict, [June 1992] (Box 3, Folder 128)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, (multiple authors)
  - (A Special Report): The New Political Environment and the Arab-Israeli Peace Process, [November 1992] (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - (A Special Report): Jerusalem, [September 1993] (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - (A Special Report): Palestinian Statehood, March, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - (A Special Report): Palestinian Self Government: An Early Assessment, April, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - (A Special Report): Whither Palestine? The Future of Democracy in Palestine, August, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - (A Special Report): Palestinian Refugees: Their Problem and Future, October, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - A Special Report, May 1995--August 1996 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - (A Special Report): The Palestine National Authority: A Critical Appraisal, May, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - (A Special Report): Settlements and Peace: The Problem of Jewish Colonization in Palestine, July, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - (A Special Report): Regional Economic Development in the Middle East: Opportunities and Risks, December, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - (A Special Report): Palestinian Elections and the Future of Palestine, March, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - (A Special Report): Beyond Rhetoric: Perspectives on a Negotiated Settlement in Palestine: Part One: Critical Issues fort he Final Status Negotiations, June, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - (A Special Report): Beyond Rhetoric: Perspectives on a Negotiated Settlement in Palestine: Part Two: Negotiating Permanent Status: What Price Peace?, August, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Information Paper, [October] 1992--September 1996 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Volume/Number: 1--7
  - (Information Paper 1): Facts and Figures about the Palestinians, October, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, Elia Zureik, Elie Sanbar
  - (Information Paper 2): The Water Issue and the Palestinian-Israeli Conflict, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, Sharif S. Elmusa
  - (Information Paper 3): Palestinian Refugee Compensation, May, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, Don Peretz
  - (Information Paper 4): Jewish Settlements, Palestinian Rights, and Peace, January, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, Ibrahim Matar
  - (Information Paper 5): Water and War in the Middle East: The Hydraulic Parameters of Conflict, July, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, Thomas R. Stauffer
  - (Information Paper 6): Palestinian Losses in 1948: The Quest for Precision, August, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, Atif Kubursi
    Volume/Number: 6
  - (Information Paper 7): The Palestinian Refugees and the Right of Return, September, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    Producer: Center for Policy Analysis on Palestine, George F. Kossaifi
  - Newsletter, January, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    Volume/Number: 3.1
  - Special Report, Winter 1992 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - In the Public Interest: An Alternative Law Review, Spring, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 133)